Hello hello dear student student today we are
going to discuss 20 everywhere se
nuts
this is
only from
some rules for all
students do students who
voted
for
you when you go out of the house then you should
hold your parents hand that the
road is always no
that sun students bilkul saaf coming
and going so you should not go alone or on
outside janta hai na aapko ki road par aisi gaadi ate jaate hai roda
student you should not go alone at the end of the road and not
run
inside the road and the same rocking on the road near the
roadways process not a student this black
and white colour
children road will be painted black and
white colour sub is very
cute but only on the way while
crossing the road only boy crossing on the
road you have to cross ad Jurassic you are
seeing useless black and white colour situation
then boxing from medical and you should
always use zebra crossing while crossing the road k
931 all will play in the same place
such park par children  Kids playing in
five always play
please like
poems where are
you how to play in place
for you now we have a place in a park very
good
for you all that
today adults for health one hat students
whenever you get hurt at the time you take
health and adult aapko hurt hoti hai in
jaruri hoti hai then you should always take help of your
parents enter when you are an adult then
you should always ask the help of blood
not always take medicine for adult
students
wwin.com.in always take medicine medicine
for adults
students but if you take it then you should always
ask the elders without asking you don't
subscribe
except asking the elders you
can't take medicine from the elders also just
stand ok don't
like
definitely
z010d
don't touch ok and distant objects which you do
n't touch
hotspot it's very dangerous
students to
not touch the heart of
playing with fire
not playing with fire on the fire  It is very
dangerous that you make powerful and this is
painful for you you should always never
touch one of the fire because
guess yourself when did it become
very painful for you know no where
students were
drawn
in
swift reply of
post then school jaana chahiye non
equil aap sakte ho just give work otherwise
you don't come back side cleaning floor
road not random the waste oil
understand ok always practice worship
and not a student made you wearing shoes be
time
tyreless when you wear choos then you are zoom
less you should always type sindh
word now and star his rule 10 so this is
good habits are watching him this is a
blank this is subscribe he is tying it well
NDA students also
certificate course this note Aayush mila you will
fall down if you
guys then you can fall ok so this tide
wait for your turn to that
i students will you go to the park always wait
for your turn and picture you
When you go to the parlor you
melt it, it's very good, very good if you don't marry
the spelling bee is coming soon to
pursue and it's very dangerous and it's also
heart for you
MP3 at the right speed both trump on the best and
share with our teachers will not with drawing
class you should not be the richest
student teacher in the class all should
not be championed on half
this fold can be possibility
student home you are all dual rules and
grand procession
that this picture quality safety rules for
everywhere
students
have a nice day